<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SamTech</title>
    <link>https://soulsy.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SamTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soulsy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build a Winning AI Strategy for Your Business</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/008/</guid>
      <description>Building a Winning AI Strategy for Your Business Source: Harvard Business Review Link to Article by Christopher Young
Among the millions who have experienced ride-sharing services via smartphone, Christopher Young reflects on how such innovation has become a part of everyday life, now thriving as an industry worth over $80 billion. Even though cars, drivers, and passengers have always existed, the introduction of smartphones has brought about new conveniences and experiences that were theoretically unimaginable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Announces New AI Startup</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/007/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/007/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Announces New AI Startup Source: BBC News - Link to Article by James Clayton
Tesla CEO Elon Musk has announced the formation of a new artificial intelligence startup named xAI. The company includes engineers who previously worked with AI powerhouses like OpenAI and Google.
Musk has been vocal about his belief that developments in AI should be paused and the sector needs regulation. He expressed that the startup was created to &amp;ldquo;understand reality&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression Model</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/linear_regression_model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/linear_regression_model/</guid>
      <description>Linear Regression Model A linear regression model is a statistical technique for modeling the relationship between an input variable and an output variable. It allows us to predict the output variable based on the values of the input variables. TensorFlow provides powerful tools for implementing and training linear regression models.
Characteristics Linear regression models capture linear relationships between input and output variables, providing a high level of interpretability. For example, in predicting housing prices, we can establish that as the size of a house increases, the price also tends to increase in a linear fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India CEO Criticized for Choosing AI Bot Over Human Staff</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/006/</guid>
      <description>India CEO Criticized for Choosing AI Bot Over Human Staff Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The CEO of an Indian firm is facing criticism after announcing that his company had replaced 90% of its support staff with an artificial intelligence (AI) chatbot. Suumit Shah, the founder of Dukaan, claimed on Twitter that the chatbot had significantly improved response and resolution times for customer queries. However, his tweet triggered outrage online, particularly in light of concerns about AI&amp;rsquo;s impact on job loss, particularly in the services industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover New Linux Kernel &#39;StackRot&#39; Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/005/</guid>
      <description>Researchers Uncover New Linux Kernel &amp;lsquo;StackRot&amp;rsquo; Privilege Escalation Vulnerability Source: The Hacker News - Link to Article
Details have emerged about a newly identified security flaw in the Linux kernel that could allow a user to gain elevated privileges on a target host.
Dubbed StackRot (CVE-2023-3269, CVSS score: 7.8), the flaw impacts Linux versions 6.1 through 6.4. There is no evidence that the shortcoming has been exploited in the wild to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Threatens Legal Action Against Meta&#39;s App Threads</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/004/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Threatens Legal Action Against Meta&amp;rsquo;s App &amp;ldquo;Threads&amp;rdquo; Source: BBC News - Link to Article
Twitter is considering legal action against Meta over its newly launched rival app, Threads. Meta claims Threads as a &amp;ldquo;friendly&amp;rdquo; alternative to Twitter, but Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Elon Musk has accused Meta of cheating. In a legal letter, Twitter alleged that former Twitter staff, now working for Meta, helped create Threads. Despite the legal dispute, Threads has gained more than 70 million users since its launch, while Twitter currently boasts an estimated 350 million users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TensorFlow Overview</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/overview/</guid>
      <description>Introduction TensorFlow is an open-source machine learning framework developed by Google. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and libraries for building and deploying machine learning models. TensorFlow helps developers define neural networks, train them, and perform numerical computations efficiently while handling large datasets. It supports multiple programming languages such as Python, C++, and Java, making it accessible to a wide range of developers. TensorFlow has gained popularity due to its flexibility, scalability, and extensive community support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploiting Unpatched WordPress Plugin Flaw to Create Secret Admin Accounts</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/003/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/003/</guid>
      <description>Hackers Exploiting Unpatched WordPress Plugin Flaw to Create Secret Admin Accounts Source: The Hacker News - Link to Article
The Hacker News reports on an ongoing attack that exploits a critical unpatched security vulnerability in the Ultimate Member plugin, putting as many as 200,000 WordPress websites at risk.
The vulnerability, identified as CVE-2023-3460 (CVSS score: 9.8), affects all versions of the Ultimate Member plugin, including the latest version 2.6.6 released on June 29, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</guid>
      <description>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The UK government is introducing new internet safety laws aimed at protecting children online, but concerns about privacy have been raised. According to the proposed Online Safety Bill, platforms that publish or allow pornographic content will be required to implement age verification measures. However, digital rights groups are questioning the transparency and data collection methods associated with these tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London Source: BBC News - Link to Article
OpenAI, the US-based company behind ChatGPT, has announced plans to open its first international office in London. The decision comes as a strategic move to attract top talent in the field of artificial intelligence (AI) and expand their research and development footprint.
OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sam Altman, expressed enthusiasm about the opportunity to tap into London&amp;rsquo;s renowned culture and exceptional talent pool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Pattern 05. Prototype Pattern</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/prototype_pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/prototype_pattern/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Prototype pattern is a design pattern that allows the creation of objects by cloning existing objects, reducing the cost of object creation. The Prototype pattern consists of the following elements:
Prototype Interface or Abstract Class: Defines the cloning method that declares the ability to clone an object. ConcretePrototype Class: Implements the Prototype interface concretely and provides the cloning method to perform object cloning. Client: Requests the cloning operation and creates new objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Pattern 04. Builder Pattern</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/builder_pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/builder_pattern/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Builder pattern is a design pattern that provides a flexible and intuitive way to create objects. It abstracts the complex object creation process and allows users to construct objects step by step.
The Builder pattern consists of the following elements:
Director: Responsible for object creation and uses the Builder interface to construct the object. Builder: Defines the interface for object creation and provides methods to build each part of the object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Pattern 03. Singleton Pattern</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/singleton_pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/singleton_pattern/</guid>
      <description>The Singleton pattern ensures that a class has only one instance of its object and provides a global access point to it.
Overview The Singleton pattern has the following characteristics:
There is only one instance of the class. It provides a global access point, allowing access to the same instance from anywhere. The Singleton pattern can be useful in various situations and is a commonly used pattern.
Advantages The Singleton pattern offers the following advantages:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Pattern 02. Abstract Factory Pattern</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/abstract_factory_pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/abstract_factory_pattern/</guid>
      <description>The Abstract Factory pattern is a design pattern that provides an interface for creating related objects, separating the responsibility of object creation. This pattern is useful when multiple objects that are related to each other need to be created, and it allows creating objects without depending on specific classes.
Overview The Abstract Factory pattern allows clients to create objects through an abstract factory interface instead of directly creating them. The abstract factory provides an interface for a set of related objects, and concrete factory classes implement this interface to create actual objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Pattern 01. Factory Pattern</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/factory_pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/dev/design_pattern/factory_pattern/</guid>
      <description>The Factory pattern is a design pattern that encapsulates object creation, providing flexibility and extensibility. This pattern allows clients to create and retrieve objects through factory methods instead of directly instantiating them.
Overview The Factory pattern involves using factory methods to create and return objects, relieving clients from the responsibility of direct object creation. By utilizing factory methods, clients can easily create objects without being aware of the complex object creation logic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to SamTech, where we delve into various topics and engage in discussions about technology. SamTech represents the number &amp;ldquo;three&amp;rdquo; (Sam in Korean), symbolizing the three key areas we focus on: News, Development, and Knowledge.
Join us on this journey of learning and information exchange as we delve into the world of technology together.
Get ready to embark on an exciting adventure with SamTech. Stay tuned for an enriching experience!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>