<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SamTech</title>
    <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SamTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soulsy.github.io/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Announces New AI Startup</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/007/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/007/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Announces New AI Startup Source: BBC News - Link to Article by James Clayton
Tesla CEO Elon Musk has announced the formation of a new artificial intelligence startup named xAI. The company includes engineers who previously worked with AI powerhouses like OpenAI and Google.
Musk has been vocal about his belief that developments in AI should be paused and the sector needs regulation. He expressed that the startup was created to &amp;ldquo;understand reality&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India CEO Criticized for Choosing AI Bot Over Human Staff</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/006/</guid>
      <description>India CEO Criticized for Choosing AI Bot Over Human Staff Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The CEO of an Indian firm is facing criticism after announcing that his company had replaced 90% of its support staff with an artificial intelligence (AI) chatbot. Suumit Shah, the founder of Dukaan, claimed on Twitter that the chatbot had significantly improved response and resolution times for customer queries. However, his tweet triggered outrage online, particularly in light of concerns about AI&amp;rsquo;s impact on job loss, particularly in the services industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover New Linux Kernel &#39;StackRot&#39; Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/005/</guid>
      <description>Researchers Uncover New Linux Kernel &amp;lsquo;StackRot&amp;rsquo; Privilege Escalation Vulnerability Source: The Hacker News - Link to Article
Details have emerged about a newly identified security flaw in the Linux kernel that could allow a user to gain elevated privileges on a target host.
Dubbed StackRot (CVE-2023-3269, CVSS score: 7.8), the flaw impacts Linux versions 6.1 through 6.4. There is no evidence that the shortcoming has been exploited in the wild to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Threatens Legal Action Against Meta&#39;s App Threads</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/004/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Threatens Legal Action Against Meta&amp;rsquo;s App &amp;ldquo;Threads&amp;rdquo; Source: BBC News - Link to Article
Twitter is considering legal action against Meta over its newly launched rival app, Threads. Meta claims Threads as a &amp;ldquo;friendly&amp;rdquo; alternative to Twitter, but Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Elon Musk has accused Meta of cheating. In a legal letter, Twitter alleged that former Twitter staff, now working for Meta, helped create Threads. Despite the legal dispute, Threads has gained more than 70 million users since its launch, while Twitter currently boasts an estimated 350 million users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploiting Unpatched WordPress Plugin Flaw to Create Secret Admin Accounts</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/003/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/003/</guid>
      <description>Hackers Exploiting Unpatched WordPress Plugin Flaw to Create Secret Admin Accounts Source: The Hacker News - Link to Article
The Hacker News reports on an ongoing attack that exploits a critical unpatched security vulnerability in the Ultimate Member plugin, putting as many as 200,000 WordPress websites at risk.
The vulnerability, identified as CVE-2023-3460 (CVSS score: 9.8), affects all versions of the Ultimate Member plugin, including the latest version 2.6.6 released on June 29, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</guid>
      <description>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The UK government is introducing new internet safety laws aimed at protecting children online, but concerns about privacy have been raised. According to the proposed Online Safety Bill, platforms that publish or allow pornographic content will be required to implement age verification measures. However, digital rights groups are questioning the transparency and data collection methods associated with these tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London Source: BBC News - Link to Article
OpenAI, the US-based company behind ChatGPT, has announced plans to open its first international office in London. The decision comes as a strategic move to attract top talent in the field of artificial intelligence (AI) and expand their research and development footprint.
OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sam Altman, expressed enthusiasm about the opportunity to tap into London&amp;rsquo;s renowned culture and exceptional talent pool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>