<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SamTech</title>
    <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SamTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soulsy.github.io/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GameOver(lay): Two Severe Linux Vulnerabilities Impact 40% of Ubuntu Users</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/013/</guid>
      <description>GameOver(lay): Two Severe Linux Vulnerabilities Impact 40% of Ubuntu Users Source: The Hacker News - Link to Article
Security researchers have recently disclosed two high-severity vulnerabilities in the Ubuntu Linux kernel that could allow attackers to gain elevated privileges on affected systems. The flaws, tracked as CVE-2023-2640 and CVE-2023-32629, reside in the OverlayFS kernel module used by Ubuntu.
Dubbed GameOver(lay) by the researchers, these vulnerabilities arise due to inadequate permissions checks in specific scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Elon Musk Right to Ditch the Twitter Bird Logo?</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/012/</guid>
      <description>Is Elon Musk Right to Ditch the Twitter Bird Logo? Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The iconic tweeting blue bird, one of the most recognizable logos on the web, is no more. Elon Musk, the billionaire, has decided to replace Twitter&amp;rsquo;s logo with an Art Deco-style X. Marketing professor Jean-Pierre Dube found this move rather perplexing, questioning the decision to abandon a well-established brand and start from scratch. While it may seem strange in the short term, could this rebranding be a strategic masterstroke in the long run?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Teases Gap-Free Hinge on Galaxy Z Flip 5</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/011/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Teases Gap-Free Hinge on Galaxy Z Flip 5 Source: 9to5Google - Link to Article
Days ahead of the Galaxy Z Flip 5&amp;rsquo;s launch, Samsung is teasing its newly-designed hinge system, which is expected to eliminate the &amp;ldquo;hinge-gap&amp;rdquo; issue seen in previous generations.
The Galaxy Z Flip 5 is set to offer significant upgrades compared to its predecessor. The front display will be over three inches, more than double the size of the Z Flip 4&amp;rsquo;s outer display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook to Make Its AI Free to Use, Expanding Access to Powerful Tech</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/010/</guid>
      <description>Facebook to Make Its AI Free to Use, Expanding Access to Powerful Tech Source: The Washington Post - Link to Article by Gerrit De Vynck and Naomi Nix
Facebook&amp;rsquo;s parent company, Meta, is taking a bold step by making its cutting-edge artificial intelligence (AI) technology, Llama 2, freely available to the public for research and product development. This &amp;ldquo;open source&amp;rdquo; approach aims to foster competition in the AI space while also raising concerns about potential misuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Threads Users Falling Away in Large Numbers, Data Suggests</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/009/</guid>
      <description>Threads Users Falling Away in Large Numbers, Data Suggests Source: Digital Trends - Link to Article by Trevor Mogg
According to recent data from analytics firm SimilarWeb, Threads, the Twitter-like app, experienced a significant decline in user engagement after its initial surge in downloads. While it garnered 100 million downloads in the first five days after launch, the number of daily active users on Android dropped from 49 million to 23.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Winning AI Strategy for Your Business</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/008/</guid>
      <description>Building a Winning AI Strategy for Your Business Source: Harvard Business Review - Link to Article by Christopher Young
Among the millions who have experienced ride-sharing services via smartphone, Christopher Young reflects on how such innovation has become a part of everyday life, now thriving as an industry worth over $80 billion. Even though cars, drivers, and passengers have always existed, the introduction of smartphones has brought about new conveniences and experiences that were theoretically unimaginable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Announces New AI Startup</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/007/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/007/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Announces New AI Startup Source: BBC News - Link to Article by James Clayton
Tesla CEO Elon Musk has announced the formation of a new artificial intelligence startup named xAI. The company includes engineers who previously worked with AI powerhouses like OpenAI and Google.
Musk has been vocal about his belief that developments in AI should be paused and the sector needs regulation. He expressed that the startup was created to &amp;ldquo;understand reality&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India CEO Criticized for Choosing AI Bot Over Human Staff</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/006/</guid>
      <description>India CEO Criticized for Choosing AI Bot Over Human Staff Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The CEO of an Indian firm is facing criticism after announcing that his company had replaced 90% of its support staff with an artificial intelligence (AI) chatbot. Suumit Shah, the founder of Dukaan, claimed on Twitter that the chatbot had significantly improved response and resolution times for customer queries. However, his tweet triggered outrage online, particularly in light of concerns about AI&amp;rsquo;s impact on job loss, particularly in the services industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover New Linux Kernel &#39;StackRot&#39; Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/005/</guid>
      <description>Researchers Uncover New Linux Kernel &amp;lsquo;StackRot&amp;rsquo; Privilege Escalation Vulnerability Source: The Hacker News - Link to Article
Details have emerged about a newly identified security flaw in the Linux kernel that could allow a user to gain elevated privileges on a target host.
Dubbed StackRot (CVE-2023-3269, CVSS score: 7.8), the flaw impacts Linux versions 6.1 through 6.4. There is no evidence that the shortcoming has been exploited in the wild to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Threatens Legal Action Against Meta&#39;s App Threads</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/004/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Threatens Legal Action Against Meta&amp;rsquo;s App &amp;ldquo;Threads&amp;rdquo; Source: BBC News - Link to Article
Twitter is considering legal action against Meta over its newly launched rival app, Threads. Meta claims Threads as a &amp;ldquo;friendly&amp;rdquo; alternative to Twitter, but Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Elon Musk has accused Meta of cheating. In a legal letter, Twitter alleged that former Twitter staff, now working for Meta, helped create Threads. Despite the legal dispute, Threads has gained more than 70 million users since its launch, while Twitter currently boasts an estimated 350 million users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploiting Unpatched WordPress Plugin Flaw to Create Secret Admin Accounts</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/003/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/003/</guid>
      <description>Hackers Exploiting Unpatched WordPress Plugin Flaw to Create Secret Admin Accounts Source: The Hacker News - Link to Article
The Hacker News reports on an ongoing attack that exploits a critical unpatched security vulnerability in the Ultimate Member plugin, putting as many as 200,000 WordPress websites at risk.
The vulnerability, identified as CVE-2023-3460 (CVSS score: 9.8), affects all versions of the Ultimate Member plugin, including the latest version 2.6.6 released on June 29, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</guid>
      <description>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The UK government is introducing new internet safety laws aimed at protecting children online, but concerns about privacy have been raised. According to the proposed Online Safety Bill, platforms that publish or allow pornographic content will be required to implement age verification measures. However, digital rights groups are questioning the transparency and data collection methods associated with these tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London Source: BBC News - Link to Article
OpenAI, the US-based company behind ChatGPT, has announced plans to open its first international office in London. The decision comes as a strategic move to attract top talent in the field of artificial intelligence (AI) and expand their research and development footprint.
OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sam Altman, expressed enthusiasm about the opportunity to tap into London&amp;rsquo;s renowned culture and exceptional talent pool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>