<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BBC on SamTech</title>
    <link>https://soulsy.github.io/tags/bbc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BBC on SamTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soulsy.github.io/tags/bbc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/002/</guid>
      <description>UK Porn Age Checks Raise Privacy Concerns Source: BBC News - Link to Article
The UK government is introducing new internet safety laws aimed at protecting children online, but concerns about privacy have been raised. According to the proposed Online Safety Bill, platforms that publish or allow pornographic content will be required to implement age verification measures. However, digital rights groups are questioning the transparency and data collection methods associated with these tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/news/001/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI to Establish International Office in London Source: BBC News - Link to Article
OpenAI, the US-based company behind ChatGPT, has announced plans to open its first international office in London. The decision comes as a strategic move to attract top talent in the field of artificial intelligence (AI) and expand their research and development footprint.
OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sam Altman, expressed enthusiasm about the opportunity to tap into London&amp;rsquo;s renowned culture and exceptional talent pool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>