<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>artificial intelligence on SamTech</title>
    <link>https://soulsy.github.io/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in artificial intelligence on SamTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soulsy.github.io/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Neural Networks (RNN)</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/recurrent_neural_networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/recurrent_neural_networks/</guid>
      <description>Recurrent Neural Networks (RNN) Recurrent Neural Networks (RNN) are a type of artificial neural network designed to recognize patterns in sequences of data, such as text, genomes, handwriting, or spoken words. Unlike traditional neural networks, RNNs have loops, allowing information to be passed from one step in the sequence to the next.
Characteristics RNNs are particularly known for their characteristic ability to &amp;ldquo;remember&amp;rdquo; previous inputs in the sequence using their hidden state, which makes them very effective for tasks that involve sequential data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN)</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/convolutional_neural_networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/convolutional_neural_networks/</guid>
      <description>Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) are a type of deep neural network that are particularly successful in processing data with a grid-like topology, such as an image. CNNs exploit spatial correlations within the data by applying a series of filters that create a hierarchical representation of the data, making them extremely efficient at image recognition and other computer vision tasks.
Characteristics Convolutional Layers: The primary building blocks of CNNs that perform a convolutional operation on the input data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/transformer_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/transformer_models/</guid>
      <description>Transformer Models Transformer models have revolutionized the field of Natural Language Processing (NLP) by introducing a new approach to handling sequence data. Developed by Vaswani et al. in the 2017 paper &amp;ldquo;Attention is All You Need,&amp;rdquo; this architecture relies heavily on self-attention mechanisms to weigh the importance of words in a sequence, thus improving the model&amp;rsquo;s understanding of the context.
Characteristics Unlike previous sequence handling models like RNNs and LSTMs that process data sequentially, transformers process all the sequence inputs simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TensorFlow Overview</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/overview/</guid>
      <description>Introduction TensorFlow is an open-source machine learning framework developed by Google. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and libraries for building and deploying machine learning models. TensorFlow helps developers define neural networks, train them, and perform numerical computations efficiently while handling large datasets. It supports multiple programming languages such as Python, C++, and Java, making it accessible to a wide range of developers. TensorFlow has gained popularity due to its flexibility, scalability, and extensive community support.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>