<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SamTech</title>
    <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SamTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/transformer_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/transformer_models/</guid>
      <description>Transformer Models Transformer models have revolutionized the field of Natural Language Processing (NLP) by introducing a new approach to handling sequence data. Developed by Vaswani et al. in the 2017 paper &amp;ldquo;Attention is All You Need,&amp;rdquo; this architecture relies heavily on self-attention mechanisms to weigh the importance of words in a sequence, thus improving the model&amp;rsquo;s understanding of the context.
Characteristics Unlike previous sequence handling models like RNNs and LSTMs that process data sequentially, transformers process all the sequence inputs simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression Model</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/linear_regression_model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/linear_regression_model/</guid>
      <description>Linear Regression Model A linear regression model is a statistical technique for modeling the relationship between an input variable and an output variable. It allows us to predict the output variable based on the values of the input variables. TensorFlow provides powerful tools for implementing and training linear regression models.
Characteristics Linear regression models capture linear relationships between input and output variables, providing a high level of interpretability. For example, in predicting housing prices, we can establish that as the size of a house increases, the price also tends to increase in a linear fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TensorFlow Overview</title>
      <link>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soulsy.github.io/knowledge/tensorflow/overview/</guid>
      <description>Introduction TensorFlow is an open-source machine learning framework developed by Google. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and libraries for building and deploying machine learning models. TensorFlow helps developers define neural networks, train them, and perform numerical computations efficiently while handling large datasets. It supports multiple programming languages such as Python, C++, and Java, making it accessible to a wide range of developers. TensorFlow has gained popularity due to its flexibility, scalability, and extensive community support.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>